Guide to the Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
- Series I. Business Records
  - Robinson Clay Product Co., Undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Rockform Corp., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Rolscreen Co., 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Roovers Bros. Inc., 1935-1939 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Rose, J. L., Wrecking Co., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Rossire, H. L., 1927 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Rotary Concrete Drill Co., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Rothschild Brothers, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Rumsey, C. J. & Co., 1937-1939, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Rumsey Ithaca Corp., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Ryan, Honorable John, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Ryerson, Joseph T. & Son, Inc., 1936-1938, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - "S" Misc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - "S" Misc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Sandura Co. Inc., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Schaefler, Leon, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Schaeffer, William H. & Sons, Inc., 1937 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Schatz Manufacturing Co., 1932 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Schickel, Gerald P., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Schickel, Norbert H.,Personal Bills, paid, 1942-1946 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Schickel, Norbert H., 1946-1957 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Schickel, Norbert H., Jr., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Schickel, Mr. William, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Scofield, Miss S. E., 1928-1932 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Scranton Bldg. Block Co., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Seamless Steel Products Corp., 1930 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Sears Roebuck & Co., 1942-1954 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Senate & House Representatives, 1945-1958 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Shannon, J. Jacob, Co., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Shelby, Carl, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Shew, Chas. E., 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Shulman, Cecil (Shulman Inc.), 1955 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Siewert Equipment Co., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Simpson, Grace, Undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Skelding, S. Merritt, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Slade, Myron K., 1953-1963 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Smith & Loveless, Inc. see Sewage Disposal Plants, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Smith, Rebe Biggs, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Smith, W. & T. Co., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Social Security Ins., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers, 1924-1929 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Co., 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Sonneborn, L. Sons, Inc., 1937-1948 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Sonoco Products Co., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Southern Tier Electrical Supply Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Spacemaster, Inc., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Stagg, C. Tracey, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Stamford, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Stamford; Connecticut Power Co., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Stamford, Conn.; town & city, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Stamford Savings Bank, 1925-1938 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Stamford Sheet Metal Works, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Stamford Water Co., 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Stamford Yacht Club, 1923, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Sprague & Henwood Inc., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Spring Hill College, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - St. Bonaventure College, 1949-1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - St. Regis Sales Corp., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Standard Electric Mfg. Co., 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Stanford-Crowell Co., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Stanley Edge Assc., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Stanley Works, 1933-1936 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - State Ins. Fund, The, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Statler Club, 1950-1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Steel and TUbes, Inc.., 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Stein, E. and Sons, Inc., 1939-1951 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Stewart Mfg. Co., 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Stickman, Herman T., Kelly, Paul, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Storm Flooring Co., 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Stringer, G. B., Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Structo Schools Corp., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Studebaker Corp., 1957- (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Stumpp & Walter Co., 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Sunray Stove Co., 1953-1961 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Swan, Theodore H., Brick & Tile Co., 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Symons Clamp & Mfg. Co., 1946-1954 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Syracuse Electric Blue Print Co., 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Syracuse General Sales Co., 1949-1955 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - T Misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Tanglefoot Co., The, 1937-1944 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Technology Club of Syracuse, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Teeter, Harpending, Fox, & F. M. Swartwood, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Telecoin Corp., 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Tenants General, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Tenants Accounts Receivable, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Tennessee Eastman Corporation, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Textileather, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Theatre for Industry, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Thermo-Con Division - Higgins Inc., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Thomas Publishing Co., 1927, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Thorne, Henry J., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Thoro System, The, 1949-1963 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Thorpe, Howard A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Thrush, H. A. Co., 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Tiffany & Co., 1925-1929, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Tilo Roofing Company, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Time Magazine, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Title Guarantee & Trust Co., 1938, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Tompkins Co. Civil Defense, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Tompkins Co. Health Dept., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Tompkins Co. Memorial Hospital, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Tompkins Co. Rationing Board, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Tompkins Co. Trust Co., 1940-1954 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Town of Ithaca Board of Assessors, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Town of Ithaca Bldg. Comm. & Zoning Officer, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Transamerican Construction Corp., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Treman, Allan H., 1938-1941, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Triple A. Accounting, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Truscon Steel Division, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Tylac Co., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - "U" Misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Union Bag & Paper Corp., 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Unit Crane & Shovel Corp., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - United American Bosch Corp., 1931 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - United Business Service, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - United Cork Co., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - USDA Liquid Assets, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - U.S. Dept. of the Interior, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - U.S. Dept. of Patents, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - U.S. Gypsum Co., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - U.S. Plywood Corp., 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - U.S. Printing Office, 1950-1961 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - U.S. Radiator Corp., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - U.S. Steel - Gen. Corres. & Info. on Orders, 1954? (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - U.S. Steel Homes, 1954-1961 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - U.S. Steel Homes - Promotion Corres., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - U.S. Steelstyle Homes - Corres. Requests for drawings, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - U.S. Steel Info. Letters, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Universal Co., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Universal Form Clamp Co., 1936-1938, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - University of Miami, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - University of the State of New York, 1932-1942 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - University Sand & Gravel Co., 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Urban Land Institute, 1950-1957 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Urqhart, Prof. L. C., 1936-1940 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - "V" Misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Van Packer Corp., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Veterans Administration, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Viglietta, Benedict P., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Vogel, H. G., Co., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - "W" Misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Wait, H. R., Co., 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Walker, Miller & Merritt, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Wall, Carl B., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Waltz, Floyd C., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - War Production Board, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Waterproofing Material, Undated (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Watson, Frank F., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Weatherlow, Hugh E., C. U. Bldgs. & Grounds, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Webcor, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Weeks, John, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - WELM, Radio Elmira Inc., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - West Hill Civic Assn., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Western Photo Engraving Co., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - WHCU, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Wheeling Corrugating Co., 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - White, C. Wilbur, 1928-1937 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - White Nurseries, 1940, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Wickwire Bros., 1938, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Wilcox Press, 1947-1962 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Willard State Hospital, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Williamson, Ellen A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Williamsburg Blacksmiths, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Wilson, J. G., Corp., 1938-1940 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Wintriss, Vie, Undated (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Wise, Wm. H. & Co., Inc., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Woodie Garber & Associates, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1941, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Wright, Long & Co., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Wright, Paul, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - WTVE-TV, Undated (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - "Y" Misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - "Z" Misc., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Zoning, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Business Records, 1919-1923 (Box 18)
- Series II. Miscellaeous Records
  - Computations for Small House, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Concrete Forms, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Draftsmen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ideas, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Investment Data, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Photocopies (Town of Ithaca), Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Political Letters, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Progress Reports, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - School Problems, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Date File - April through July, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Date File - Aug. through Sept. 3, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Date File - Jan., Feb., March, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Date File - April, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Answers from Salesmen, etc, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Bailey-Drake Co., 1915 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Ball Bearings, etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Berling, W. C., 1924 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Bournemann's Sons, Louis, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Bradstreet's, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Building, etc., 1925 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Central Alloy Steel Co., 1929 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Univ. Club, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1908-1915 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1925-1928 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Carbons & Letters, 1926-1929 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Cummings & Lockwood & Walter Maguire, 1913-1925 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Economic & Efficiency Methods, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Fairbank, Clair W., 1916 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Fifth Ave. Bank, 1911-1916 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Fish, Richardson & Neave, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - 500 Mile Race, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Fleming, William J., Jr., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Form Materials, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Franklin, The H. H., Mfg. Co., 1909 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Franklin Meetings, 1909-1910 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Frasse, Peter A, & Co., Inc., 1923-1931 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Hopkins, L. A., 1916 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Hoyt, Charles W. (adv.), 1912 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Hume-Mansur Building, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Hummer, J. L., 1916 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Huntington, H. R., 1911-1913 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Indian Motorcycle Co., 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Ivins, Mason, Wolff & Hoguet, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Kuttroff, Adolf, 1916-1919 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Letters to Answer, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Linde Air Products, 1927-1929 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Locks (re), 1926 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Lord and Thomas, Adv., 1915 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Lynham, Frank, 1910-1911 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Matheson Co., 1929 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - McDonnell, John B., 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - McKendrick, Sigma Nu Lodge, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Middlebrook & Borland, 1924-1926 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Munn & Co., 1910-1912 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Nixon, N., c/o The Standard Motor Const. Co., 1913 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Pinzon, Carlos, 1922-1923 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Piston Rings, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Prentiss, Henry, & Co., 1926-1928 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Rome Mfg. Co., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Rossire, Henry L., 1922-1923 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Sager, The J. H.,Co., 1910 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Sasseen, Robert A., Undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Soc. of Automobile Engineers, 1910-1926 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Stamford Yacht Club, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Stop Light, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Thomas Auto Truck Co., Inc., 1916 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Tools, etc., 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Vogel, Edwin A., and others - letters to, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Wallace Barnes Co., Albert S. Wells, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Wheeler, C. D., 1916 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Whidden, Guy C., (Adv.), 1915 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Whitehead Metal Products Co., International Nickel, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Blueprints, Charts, Undated (Box 19)
- Series III. Schickel Moter Co. Records
  - Advertisements, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bills & Receipts, 1923-1924 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Blueprints: Camshaft Rocker Lever, Carburetor..., 1917, 1918, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Brick, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cards, notes, etc., Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Census, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Combination Trial Balance & P&S Statements, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Copy for Motorcycle Whirlwind Folder, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Cylinder Finishing Tool, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Drawing List in 3 Sections, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Drawings, Calculations, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Drawings, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Factory, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1916, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Florida, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Intake Air Measurements, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - International Silver Co. Lab., Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lists, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
  - Manifolds, Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Manning, Maxwell & Moore, Inc., 1918 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Market Production & Earning Possibilities, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Material Lists, 1916-1918 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Sales Material & Reports, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1917-1918 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Motor Bus Show, 1925-11 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Motorcycle Catalogs, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Mounting for Vehicle Wheel (patent), Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Oiler & other parts, 1922-1924 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Paige Circular, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Parts Lists, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36-37)
  - Parts Price List, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Patent Infringements (Harley-Davidson), 1926-1927 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Patents, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Patents, copies of patents, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Plan of Organization, Directions for opening mail, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Quotations on Oiler Parts, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Radio, 1925-11 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Receipts, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Receipts, 1910-1911 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Receipts, Sept.-Dec., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Refrigeration, electric, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Refrigerator, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Report on... Double Conical Roller Bearings, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Schickel Motor Co., stocks, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Schickel Motor Co. in "American Machinist", 1920 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Schickel Motorcylce brochures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Schickel Motorcycle, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Shaw Mfg. Co., 1920-1922 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Simplex, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Smith & Serrell, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Specification Sheets, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Subdivisions, etc. (Dearborn, Mich.), Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Traffic Control Systems, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Treat, S. W., 1915-1918 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Treat Mss., Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - USN Bids, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Water Closet Toilet, Undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Business & Financial Records, Undated (Box 11)
  - Sales Department Reports, 1916 (Box 11)
  - Checkbooks, Bank Book, 1908-1918 (Box 11)
  - Record Book, 1916 (Box 11)
  - Time Book, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Specification and Machine Record Book (notebook), 1912-1913 (Box 11)
  - State lists: counties, dealers (notebook), 1912 (Box 11)
  - Machine Parts list (bound), Undated (Box 11)
  - Finished Cost Sheets, 1917-1918 (Box 11)
  - Finished Cost Sheets, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Checkbooks & Passbooks, 1908-1910 (Box 11)
  - Cash Book (notebook), 1905 (Box 11)
  - Gas Engine, Internal combustion Engine, 1907-1909 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Constant Volume Engine, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Constant Compression Engine, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cummings & Lockwood, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Patents, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 5-9)
  - Patents, General Data, 1908-1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Patents, 1914-1927 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Tank Assembly, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Mud Guard Patents, 1913-1916 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Mud Guard Patents, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
  - Air Cleaners, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Indian Motorcycle Co., 1916, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Motorcycle Illustrated (photocopies), 1911-1912 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Licensing, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Front Fork Patent, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - Charge Treating Device for Internal Combustion Engines, 1915-1916 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Windshield, 1925-1926 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Oil Gauge, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Oil Gauge, 1925-1927 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Flat Base Oiler, Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Trego Motor Corp., Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Patents, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Dial Lock, Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Contracts and Advertising, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Camshaft, 1918-1919 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Oil Gauge - Reference Patents, etc., Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Application for Patent on Oil Gauge, Undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Incorporation of the Schickel Motor Co., 1911-1913 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Patent Drawings - Photostats, Undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Two-speed Assembly, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Motorcycle Advertisements, Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Motorcycle Assembly, Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Patent-Mounting for Vehicle Wheels, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Expense Figures, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Searches - Intake Manifords, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - USN supplies bid forms, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Blueprint - Model of 1918 (Filloux) Split Rings, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Advertising, Undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Assignment of Patents, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Miscellany, Undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous Patents, Undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Taxes, 1918-1922 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Orders, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - John H. McCready - Manifold, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Schickel Motorcycles material (Box 20)
- Series IV. Personal Papers
  - Bills, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Data: Norbert H. Schickel, Sr., Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Boating, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Broadside (copy), Wagner-Ellender-Taft Bill, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - College of Sacred Heart: The Essay; essay by Ruth Schickel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Public Works of the State of New York, Div. of Canals & Waterways, 1930-1937 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Family,Friends, 1912-1930 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Gleason, McLanahan, Merritt & Ingraham, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gleason, Vogel & Proskauer, 1920-1925 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Guardianship related papers, 1916-1940 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Hanna, Matthew E., Jr., & others - leassor of Shippan House, 1931-1933 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Income Tax, 1918-1923 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Insurance, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mss.: "The Research Executive", 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Maps - Street Guides, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - NYC Property, 1934, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Personal, 1916-1937 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Personal, 1927-1940 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Port Huron Cottage, 1925-1926 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Schools, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Scrip (Notre Dame), cover & drawings by W. J. Schickel, 1940, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - (N.H.S.) Thesis Blueprints, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - (N.H.S.) Thesis Mss., Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - (N.H.S.) Thesis - old notes, rewritten, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Title Guarantee Trust Co., 1920 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Travel - Tours - Resorts, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26-28)
  - Unanswered Letters., 1925 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Zema, Rev. Demetrius B., talks at Fordham, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - "The Counsel of Virginity" essay by Ruth M. (?) Schickel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Mss. - Ruth M. Schickel Thesis, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Ruth M. Schickel, bound thesis, 1936, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Certificates, 1904, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Cancelled checks, misc. receipts, Undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Diaries, address book, 1936, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Diary notebook, with tenant records, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous diaries & notes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Notes - Regional Sales Clinic, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Decrees on Accounting & Resignation of Guardian, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Expenses, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Expense Figures, 1925-1926, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Insurance, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers, 1918-1927 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Life Extension Institute, 1922-1928 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mss. re building, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Memorandum of Agreement (Schickel-Carruthers), 1933 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Printed, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Mss. re building, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Shippan Point House, 1905-1928 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Shippan Point House, 1929-1934 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Taxes, 1922-1928 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Thesis abstract - Mss., Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Drafting Equipment, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Scale Model Boats, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Boats, Aviation, Motors, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Campers & Camping Equipment, Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Campers & Camping Equipment, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Motorcycles, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Automobiles, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Electric Trucks, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - About Autos and Parts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - About Autos and Parts, Motors, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - About Autos and Parts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Home & Personal, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Homes, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Date unknown (Box 17)